Ah! Ah!
Oh! Orine!
Ah!
They're coming!
Sakura!
Why?
I came back far earlier than the promised time when the cherry blossoms bloom, but...
But...
No!
Orine!
Magisa!
Shh!
Ah!
Are you okay?
Yeah!
Let's run!
Ah!
I can't believe I was making the machine!
And attacked my beloved zero-zero!
Ah!
But you didn't know anything!
I'm the one who deserves the blame.
What?
My father's company forced you to make those machines.
So this is all my fault.
That's ridiculous.
This has nothing to do with you.
Then it's got nothing to do with you either.
Chiri.
But I never thought...
I never thought she would hurt anyone.
Chiri, I...
I'm sorry, Orene.
You don't have to do anything.
I'll be the one to destroy them.
Chiri!
Can I really let it end here?
I don't want to lose here.
Not like this.
And not today.
Chiri!
Hurry! Now's your chance!
Okay!
There's a car out by the rear gate!
Gotta move fast!
Everyone's gathering there!
Thank you.
Let's go, Orene.
Sakura...
Orine! Chiri!
Nagisa!
Thank goodness you're okay.
Come this way, please.
We'll take you all to the flying gate immediately.
You'll be safe there.
There's no way!
I'm going to save my dad!
I can't let you put yourselves in danger.
But because of me, my dad...
Nagisa, I'll help you.
Kanata-san...
We can't allow anything to interfere with the concert.
We've trained for combat in order to protect those who love entertainment.
It's our duty.
As members of 0048.
We're going, ladies!
Yes!
Hold on.
Kanata-san...
Remember, your father's blood is in your veins as well.
Did you know my father?
Yes.
He's a legend among us.
And to all of those who continue fighting for their freedom.
Really?
Dad must have been amazing!
Yes, he was.
Really amazing!
Change of plans!
We're going to help these girls!
Go out and rescue Nagisa-san's father!
Got it?
Yes, sir!
That day...
My heart was pounding as I ran through the subway.
That voice...
Announcing the start of the concert...
Ow!
Our dream...
Was born here.
That's the entrance to the detention facilities.
Anti-entertainment forces keep their prisoners underground there.
This abandoned mine leads to the basement of the detention facility.
We'll attack from outside and create a diversion to draw the attention of the guards who are on duty.
While they're confused, you'll all enter through the basement.
Just be careful.
So this is a distraction tactic, then.
I'm gonna go with Wota!
Yuka!
It's too dangerous!
Don't do it!
What?
But why not?
You're all working so hard, I want to help, too!
For Nagisa and for your planet!
I want to help, so will you please just let me!
Yuka...
I'll be going with you, alright?
Kaneda-san!
Nagisa, promise me you'll rescue your father, okay?
Okay!
Whoa!
Looks to me like there's even more than usual.
They may be on guard with the concert coming up.
Mamoru, what's the matter?
Why are you being so reckless?
What if you get hurt or something?
You're an idol.
Everyone's waiting for you guys.
You need to be more aware of that!
We're on a mission, Big Mouth!
You're the one who needs to be aware of that.
I know, jeez!
Roger that.
They've arrived at the infiltration point.
Is it zero zero?
They're over here!
Go left, up ahead.
Left, left.
Uh, Sonata!
Megu!
Dad?
Hmm?
Daddy!
Nagisa, what are you doing here?
Thank goodness!
I'm getting you out of here!
Stand back!
It's dangerous!
Don't do this, Nagisa!
I'm not going to leave this place with you.
What?
I'll talk to the higher-ups myself.
Why?
I just...
Why not?
I'm a member of the Entertainment Administration Bureau.
I can't go with an entertainment supporter
who turned their back on Lancaster.
So leave.
Just go!
But Dad...
Yes?
They've been alerted that you're there.
You've got to retreat!
Nagisa!
Nagisa-san!
I said go!
Dad!
That's one more bowl of rice
and one with a little extra.
Yuka, eat up!
Eat it!
Yeah, I'll eat later, okay?
Look, you've got food on your face!
Thank you for waiting!
We should be safe here.
Yuka's family has always been good to Woda.
They make sure to take care of us.
They let us have as much rice as we want.
They'll even give us pork soup
instead of miso soup.
Good news!
Because of the coating on your clothes,
your injury is shallow.
But I...
I can't go on stage looking like this.
I wanted to be up there with Yoko.
I'm sure you'll have another chance.
Come on, you could have told me!
I still don't understand why you didn't bother
to tell me anything about Lancaster and your letters.
I'm so sorry, darling,
but we thought you would worry and didn't want to...
Sir, ma'am!
Huh?
Please tell me.
Is it my fault my father was taken to the detention facility?
Just tell me!
In the beginning,
we tried fooling them with lies, but...
They didn't fall for it.
Your father was told to make you quit.
It's not your fault.
Motomiya-san was stubborn.
And he refused.
Huh?
We're almost at your house, Nagisa.
Yeah.
Do you want to go see your mom?
It's okay.
I'd just cause her trouble
more than I already have.
Mom...
She always took such good care of them.
I can't get a nice color
because of all the smoke from the factories.
You should get some flowers
that are easier to grow.
The added effort makes them precious.
Just like you, Nagisa.
I'm sorry.
Because of me.
Dad and Mom are...
I'm sorry.
Take Megumi to the infirmary.
The rest of you get to your lessons immediately.
There's no time.
Okay.
Let's start with Nagisa on Cherry.
Cherry, Cherry boy.
Oh, oh.
Nagisa?
Nagisa, what's wrong?
It must be psychological.
It's happened before.
A tremendous amount of stress
can make someone lose their voice.
But...
The concert is tomorrow.
There's no time.
We can do something
about all of the other songs
on the set list
by assigning Nagisa's part
to someone else.
But it won't work
for Nagisa no Cherry.
Let me sing it, Tsubasa-san.
Cherry?
I've been practicing with her
this whole time.
I have the lyrics
and the solo choreography memorized.
Hey, Chiri.
Do you think you can?
Yes.
Please let me do it.
Hmm, fine then.
Nagisa, you'll be a backup dancer.
For the other songs,
Nagisa's parts.
I'll do it.
Me too.
Nagisa, it'll be okay.
Leave it to us.
Oh...
Unh...
Uf...
Unh?
Unh...
Hmm?
Hmm.
S-Quadruple's lost it.
I don't think this song's good at all.
You go.
I hate this song.
The Next Generation?
It makes it sound like there's something wrong with ours,
and there's not.
We're good.
It totally sucks.
Takamina, are you okay?
You've got a terrible fever.
I'm fine.
I'm still feeling the effects of what happened then.
Why didn't you say anything?
I'm okay.
I'm taking medicine to stop the pain.
Besides, I'm thinking of graduating from Zero Zero
after we're done with this concert.
What?
It's just my dream is to entrust the group
to Kaneda.
Now it's her turn.
Takamina.
Wrong!
Yuka, how many times do I have to tell you?
You have to drill Nagisa's part into your head!
Sorry!
Orine, you too!
Sing louder!
Every one of you have to imagine you're singing for Nagisa too!
Okay!
Because I can't sing, I'm causing everyone so much trouble.
I'm making Dad and Mom suffer.
It's all my fault.
It's coming together.
Yes, somehow.
Good work, everyone.
There isn't much time left before the concert, so get some rest.
Okay!
Thank you very much!
Shhh!
You're looking for Tsubasa-san?
Nagisa, are you thinking about graduating from Zero Zero?
You're the one who said Zero Zero isn't about winning or losing.
But I still disagree.
I feel like that would be running away.
I feel like I would be turning away from my potential.
I won't try to stop you from graduating from Zero Zero.
But please, Nagisa.
If you're going to graduate from Zero Zero,
at least do it after dancing behind me.
Quit after you've lost to me.
You are not going out now!
Not until you do that!
There's no way I'm going to lose to you!
Not now, and not ever!
You got that, Nagisa?
The trainee concert will begin now!
Put all the strength you have into this concert.
Don't hold anything back!
Right!
Woda, your strength is their courage,
and their courage is your strength.
Thank you for your assistance!
Go there!
Let's go there!
While the concert is moving forward,
let's go over our guard arrangements.
First, when the concert begins,
I would like all of you to…
Oh, hey, Yuka!
What's wrong?
Mamoru, thank you!
I know that there's a lot going on right now,
but I promise I'll make it a great concert, okay?
Yeah, do that!
I look forward to it!
I don't know…
Seems like a dream!
I mean, you're a member of Woda now,
and things are different.
Oh, hey, Yuka!
What's wrong?
Mamoru, thank you!
I know that there's a lot going on right now,
but…
But I promise I'll make it a great concert, okay?
Yeah, do that!
I look forward to it!
I don't know…
It seems like a dream!
Hm?
I mean, you're a member of Woda now,
and things are different.
Remember back when you told me
that you couldn't love me
if I became an idol?
I don't feel that way anymore.
What?
I'm in love with you
as a member of Zero-Zero.
Huh?
Mamoru!
But…
But I could never honestly love you
if you weren't in the group.
What?
So then…
I'll support you forever.
And you told me
when you told me
that you couldn't love me
if I became an idol.
I don't feel that way anymore.
What?
I'm in love with you
as a member of Zero-Zero.
Huh?
Oh…
Mamoru?
But…
Huh?
But I could never honestly love you…
If you weren't in the group!
What?
So then…
I'll support you forever.
As a fan of who you are in Zero-Zero.
Mamoru!
It's time to meet up!
You're late!
Okay!
So…
Give it all you got!
Do your best,
and we'll protect the stage for you!
What are you doing?
Everyone's waiting for you!
Sorry!
Yuka-san!
Where have you been?
Sorry!
Yuka-san!
Where have you been?
Sorry!
Okay, let's circle up!
Ready, and…
We are always grateful!
Calmly, carefully, and correctly!
May our audience smile!
And may we make everyone happy!
May our audience smile…
That's right!
Let's go!
AKB-0048!
EL-E-E-E-E-E!
W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W-W!
If you enjoyed your audience smile…
That's right!
Let's go!
AKB-0048!
A-K-B-0048!
We are always happy!
You ready to thank my audience!
You ready to join us,
you ready to join us?
They're coming.
Good evening, everyone!
Nice to meet you!
We're the AKB-048!
Newest out of trainees!
I want you!
This is our first-ever trainee concert!
We're all a little bit nervous,
but we're hoping that all of you will enjoy our entertainment.
And Zero Zero!
Thank you!
Listen to our song, Ogoe Diamond!
走り出すバス追いかけて
Thank goodness Mamoru and the others are guarding the stage for us.
Got it! Amazing!
This isn't good. They're serious this time.
I... I've probably always had these feelings for you.
I've always kept them, inside my heart!
All units retreat now!
What?
The concert's cancelled!
You're kidding!
Goodbye, Honoru.
Oh, poor Ine!
A new Kira...
We promise we'll be back!
It's a steady sound of followers!
Still logical!
You're almostware!
No one wants to make qualcosa on!
movie
Some music
ORGAN PLAYS